YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS FILES
  - Subseries A. Historical Files
    - New York
      - Rochester and Monroe County
        - Management Study and Facility Analysis, Nov 1981 (Box 872, Folder 14)
      - Suffolk County (Bay Shore), 1929-66
        - General, 1929-66, n.d. (Box 872, Folder 15-16)
        - Board of Directors: minutes and reports, 1944-53 (Box 873, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1947-53, n.d. (Box 873, Folder 2)
        - Finance Campaign, 1947, 1949-52, n.d. (Box 873, Folder 3-4)
      - Utica
        - General, 1873, 1956 (Box 873, Folder 5)
        - The Christian Worker, 1882-86 (Box 873, Folder 6)
      - Westchester and Putnam County (Katonah), 1927-39 (Box 873, Folder 7)
      - White Plains, 1988-96, n.d. (Box 873, Folder 8)
    - North Carolina
      - Miscellaneous, 1922-23, 1970 (Box 873, Folder 9)
      - Salisbury, 1948-52 (Box 873, Folder 10)
    - North Dakota: Grand Forks, 1967-70 (Box 873, Folder 11)
    - Ohio
      - Miscellaneous, 1969-86 (Box 873, Folder 12)
      - Ashtabula County, 1964-74, n.d. (Box 873, Folder 13)
      - Cambridge, 1928-34 (Box 873, Folder 14)
      - Cincinnati
        - General, 1911-93, n.d. (Box 873, Folder 15)
        - Centennial, 1968 (Box 873, Folder 16)
        - Strategic planning: report "Laying the Foundations for the Future," 1976 (Box 874, Folder 1)
        - Women's Christian Association
          - Annual Report, 1869, 1870, 1871 (Box 874, Folder 2)
          - Annual Report, including Annual Report of the Young Ladies' Branch, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875 (Box 874, Folder 3)
          - Annual Report, 1876, 1877, 1879, 1880, 1880, 1881, 1883, 1884, 1884-5, 1886, 1888, 1889, 1891 (Box 874, Folder 4-7)
          - Young Ladies' Branch/Protestant Industrial Branch: annual reports, 1876-77 (Box 874, Folder 8)
        - Young Women's Christian Association
          - Year Book, 1903, 1911, 1913-15 (Box 874, Folder 9)
          - Reports by Eva Bowles, 1934 (Box 874, Folder 10)
      - Cleveland
        - General, 1869-1997, n.d. (Box 874, Folder 11-12)
        - Centennial, 1968 (Box 874, Folder 13)
        - History
          - "After Thirty Years: Telling of the Daily Doings, Multiform Methods and Departments of the Young Women's Christian Association of Cleveland," souvenir publication, 1899 (Box 874, Folder 14)
          - "Women Involved in the Real World" compiled by Mildred H. Esgar, first draft, prepared for centennial observance, 1968 (Box 875, Folder 1-4)
        - International Institute, 1940, n.d. (Box 875, Folder 5)
      - Dayton, 1944-75, n.d. (Box 875, Folder 6)
      - Lancaster-Fairfield County, 1971-85 (Box 875, Folder 7)
      - Montgomery County, 1927-30 (Box 875, Folder 8)
      - Ohio District, 1950-69 (Box 875, Folder 9)
      - Toledo: report "Today and Tomorrow at the Toledo YWCA," May 1972 (Box 875, Folder 10)
      - Youngstown, 1975, 1980
        - General 1950-80 (Box 875, Folder 11)
        - Reports1950-51
          - Executive Director (Box 875, Folder 12-14)
          - Branch Business, Professional, and Industrial Club (Box 875, Folder 15)
          - Health Education Council (Box 875, Folder 16)
          - Homemakers' Club (Box 875, Folder 17)
          - Junior Business Women Group (Box 875a, Folder 1-3)
          - Supervisory conferences with staff
            - Marie Hedgeland (Box 875a, Folder 4)
            - Lillian Jackson (Box 875a, Folder 5)
            - Marjorie Mariner (Box 875a, Folder 6)
            - Lucille Smith (Box 875a, Folder 7)
            - Eleanor Stehman (Box 875a, Folder 8)
            - Julia Westfall (Box 875a, Folder 9)
            - Doris V. Wilson (Box 875a, Folder 10)
            - Y-Teen Department (Box 875a, Folder 11-12)
            - Branch YW-Wives (Box 875a, Folder 13-14)
    - Oklahoma
      - Miscellaneous 1925, 1974 (Box 875, Folder 15)
      - Kaleidoscope: Program Materials for YWCA Councils in Oklahomaundated (Box 875, Folder 16)
      - McAlester 1928-33 (Box 875, Folder 17)
      - North East Oklahoma District1927-29 (Box 875, Folder 18)
      - Oklahoma District1942-59 (Box 875a, Folder 19)
      - Okmulgee1948-53 (Box 875a, Folder 20)
      - Sapulpa1945-60 (Box 875a, Folder 21)
      - Tri-state District1930 (Box 875a, Folder 22)
      - Tulsa District1917-30 (Box 875a, Folder 23)
    - Oregon
      - Astoria1949-61 (Box 875a, Folder 24)
      - Baker1927-29 (Box 875a, Folder 25)
      - Central Lane YWCA of Eugene1950-67 (Box 875a, Folder 26)
      - Medford1931-32 (Box 875a, Folder 27)
      - Portland1874, 1976-83 (Box 875a, Folder 28)
      - Salem1949 (Box 875a, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Miscellaneous, 1889-2000 (Box 876, Folder 1)
      - Bethlehem, 1959-97 (Box 876, Folder 2)
      - Easton, 1950-80 (Box 876, Folder 3)
      - Germantown, 1970-80 (Box 876, Folder 4)
      - Hanover, 1974-90, n.d. (Box 876, Folder 5)
      - Harrisburg
        - General, 1974-80 (Box 876, Folder 6)
        - Report of the 1954-55 Study of the Harrisburg YWCA (Box 876, Folder 7)
      - Hollidaysburg, 1928-54 (Box 876, Folder 8)
      - Kane, 1950-67 (Box 876, Folder 9)
      - Lancaster, 1954, 1998 (Box 876, Folder 10)
      - Philadelphia
        - General, 1897-1998, n.d. (Box 876, Folder 11-12)
        - Centennial, 1969-70 (Box 876, Folder 13)
        - Manual: "YWCA Property Administration," Oct 1978 (Box 876, Folder 14)
        - Reports
          - Women's Christian Association of Philadelphia Annual Report, 1870, 1874, 1877, 1883 (Box 876, Folder 15-16)
          - "100 Years Plus: The Philadelphia Plan" by Rhetta Arter, 1970 (Box 876, Folder 17)
      - Pittsburgh
        - General, 1911-12, 1940-92, n.d. (Box 877, Folder 1-3)
        - Centennial, 1967 (Box 877, Folder 4)
        - Reports
          - Women's Christian Association of Pittsburgh and Allegheny: annual reports, 1875, 1875, 1876, 1877 (Box 877, Folder 5-6)
          - "The Administrative Process Used in Planning the Total Program of a Group Work Agency" by Mildred Savacool, 1950 (Box 877, Folder 7)
          - Self-Appraisal Report, 1952 (Box 877, Folder 8)
      - Reading: Cook Book, n.d. (Box 877, Folder 9)
      - Turtle Creek, 1928-30 (Box 877, Folder 10)
      - Wilkes-Barre, 1971-80 (Box 877, Folder 11)
      - Williamsport, 1872, 1971 (Box 877, Folder 12)
      - Wilmerding, 1927-43 (Box 877, Folder 13)
      - York, 1951-53, n.d. (Box 877, Folder 14)
    - Rhode Island: general, 1877, 1935-75 (Box 877, Folder 15)
    - South Carolina
      - Aiken County, 1954-60 (Box 877, Folder 16)
      - Charleston, 1959, 1967 (Box 877, Folder 17)
      - Columbia
        - Phyllis Wheatley Branch study, 1958 (Box 877, Folder 18)
        - Visitation reports, 1941-47 (Box 877, Folder 19)
      - Greenville, 1967, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 1)
      - Spartanburg, 1929-31 (Box 878, Folder 2)
      - Sumter, 1966-82 (Box 878, Folder 3)
    - South Dakota
      - Aberdeen, 1977-82 (Box 878, Folder 4)
      - Rapid City, 1948-61 (Box 878, Folder 5)
      - South Dakota District, 1927-28 (Box 878, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee
      - Miscellaneous, 1961-97, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 7)
      - Bristol, 1971-79 (Box 878, Folder 8)
      - Chattanooga, 1973-93 (Box 878, Folder 9)
      - Memphis, 1945-68 (Box 878, Folder 10)
      - Oak Ridge, 1958-95, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 11)
      - Tennessee District, 1951-56, [see also Kentucky District] (Box 878, Folder 12)
    - Texas
      - Miscellaneous, 1956-81, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 13)
      - Amarillo, 1969-77 (Box 878, Folder 14)
      - Austin, 1913-88, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 15)
      - Beaumont: cook book, 1976 (Box 878, Folder 16)
      - Dallas, 1978-79 (Box 878, Folder 17)
      - Dallas District, 1928-30 (Box 878, Folder 18)
      - Galveston, 1977-84 (Box 878, Folder 19)
      - Houston
        - General, 1969-88 (Box 878, Folder 20)
        - A Manual for Leaders, 1971-72 (Box 878, Folder 21)
      - Houston-Gulf Coast District (Angleton), 1949-64 (Box 878, Folder 22)
      - Lower Rio Grande Valley (Mercedes), 1928-47 (Box 878, Folder 23)
      - Odessa, 1967-72 (Box 878, Folder 24)
      - Oil Belt District, 1928-29 (Box 878, Folder 25)
      - San Antonio, 1977-91, n.d. (Box 878, Folder 26)
    - Virginia
      - Lynchburg, 1984 (Box 878, Folder 27)
      - Norfolk (Tidewater Area)
        - General, 1961-74 (Box 879, Folder 1)
        - Phyllis Wheatley Branch study, 1959 (Box 879, Folder 2)
      - The Peninsula (Newport News), 1918-90 (Box 879, Folder 3)
      - Portsmouth, 1928-31 (Box 879, Folder 4)
      - Richmond: thesis '"Helping Others Help Themselves": Social Advocacy and Wage-Earning Women in Richmond, Virginia, 1910-32' by Elizabeth Stevens Brinson, 1984 (Box 879, Folder 5-6)
      - Staunton, 1927-30 (Box 879, Folder 7)
    - Washington
      - Miscellaneous, 1976-79 (Box 879, Folder 8)
      - Centralia, 1929-31 (Box 879, Folder 9)
      - Everett, 1927-31 (Box 879, Folder 10)
      - Seattle, 1964-84 (Box 879, Folder 11)
      - Seattle-King County, 1976, 1981, n.d. (Box 879, Folder 12)
      - Tacoma: Directional Study, "To Chart a Course," 1968 (Box 879, Folder 13)
      - Tri-City YWCA of Kennewick, Pasco, and Richland/Richland, 1951-61 (Box 879, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin
      - State, 1890, n.d. (Box 879, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976-78 (Box 879, Folder 16)
      - Green Bay-De Pere: History, 1919-68 (Box 879, Folder 17-18)
      - Madison, 1918, 1927, 1992 (Box 879, Folder 19)
      - Milwaukee
        - General, 1973-92, n.d. (Box 879, Folder 20)
        - Reports
          - "Priorities and Potentials for Program Development," 1966 (Box 879, Folder 21)
          - "Internal Operations," 1966 (Box 880, Folder 1)
      - Neenah-Menasha, 1968-77 (Box 880, Folder 2)
      - Sheboygan, 1954-64 (Box 880, Folder 3)
    - Wyoming, 1926-79 (Box 880, Folder 4)
    - OVERSIZE (Box 880)
      - Ohio, Cleveland: The Earnest Worker, Jun 1880-May 1886 [incomplete] (Box 881)
      - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia: Faith and Works, September 1875-August 1888 (Box 882-884)
      - Tennessee, Memphis: The Gleaner, Nov 1881-Oct 1886 (Box 885)
      - New York, City of
        - General and history
          - General, 1885, 1889, 1932-98, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 1-2)
          - Thesis "The YWCA of the City of New York, 1870-1920" by Helen Bittar, New York University, 1979 (Box 886, Folder 3-5)
        - Archives, Laura Parsons Pratt Research Center, 1974-87 (Box 886, Folder 6)
        - Branches and Residences/Buildings
          - General, 1974-88, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 7)
          - Flushing, 1991-98 (Box 886, Folder 8)
          - Harlem/Upper Manhattan/New Harlem, 1903-77, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 9)
          - Headquarters, 7 East 15th St., 1988-94, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 10)
          - International Institute, 113 East 34th St., 1912-40, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 11)
          - Margaret Louisa Home (residence), 14 East 16th St., 1904-11, n.d. (Box 886, Folder 12)
          - Studio Club (residence & social center for artists), 210 E 77th St., 1926, 1973, 1977 (Box 886, Folder 13)
          - West Side, 1937 (Box 886, Folder 14)
        - Joint Campaign to Raise $4,000,000 for the YWCA and the YMCA of the City of New York, 1913 (Box 886, Folder 15)
        - Annual Reports/Record of the Year
          - Bound copies
            - 1871-1916 (Box 887)
            - With additional materials bound in, 1871-1913 (Box 888-889)
          - Unbound copies, 1871-72, 1874-75, 1879, 1882, 1907-19 (Box 890-891)
        - Ladies' Christian Association/Union of the City of New York (precursor organization)
          - General, 1882, 1975 (Box 892)
          - Annual reports, 1860-61, 1866-70, 1872-91, 1891-1902, 1904-08 (Box 892)
  - Subseries B. 1988-2002
    - Alabama
      - Birmingham
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 893)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-98 (Box 893)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 893)
        - Board of Directors, 1991 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996-99 (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 893)
        - Program, 1983-99, n.d. (Box 893)
      - Mobile
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 893)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-95 (Box 893)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995-96 (Box 893)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 893)
        - Board of Directors, 1992 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1972, 1996 (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1991-98, n.d. (Box 893)
        - Program, 1990-97, n.d. (Box 893)
    - Alaska
      - Anchorage
        - Accreditation requirements, 1993-99 (Box 893)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 893)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-96 (Box 893)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1989-96, n.d. (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1979-2000 (Box 893)
        - Program, 1987-99, n.d. (Box 893)
    - Arizona
      - Bisbee
        - Accreditation requirements, 1992-94 (Box 893)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-96 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994 (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 893)
        - Program, 1997-99, n.d. (Box 893)
      - Douglas
        - Accreditation requirements, 1993-96. n.d. (Box 893)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-96 (Box 893)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 893)
        - Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1978, 1989-2000 (Box 893)
      - Maricopa County (Phoenix)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 893)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 893)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993-98 (Box 893)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 893)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-2000 (Box 893)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1961-99 (Box 893)
        - Correspondence, 1981-2000 (Box 893)
        - Finance administration, 1988-99 (Box 893)
        - Program, 1995-99, n.d. (Box 893)
      - Tucson
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 894)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 894)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-97 (Box 894)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 894)
        - Board of Directors, 1987-96 (Box 894)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1969, 1996 (Box 894)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 894)
        - Legal: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission v. YWCA of Tucson and YWCA of the USA
          - General and correspondence, 1988-93 (Box 894)
          - Defendants' affidavits in opposition to motion of plaintiff for summary judgment (Box 894)
          - Exhibits (Box 895)
          - Mailing to member associations, 1992 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1988-99 (Box 895)
    - Arkansas
      - Bess Chisum Stephens/Greater Little Rock (Little Rock)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 895)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 895)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-98 (Box 895)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1973, 1995-1996 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 895)
      - El Dorado
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 895)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 895)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-97 (Box 895)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000-01 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995-96 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2002, n.d. (Box 895)
        - Program, 1984-93, n.d. (Box 895)
      - Fort Smith
        - Accreditation requirements, 1988-93 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1978, 1989-91 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1977-93 (Box 895)
        - Disaffiliation, 1991-93 (Box 895)
        - Finance administration, 1988 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1989-92 (Box 895)
      - Hot Springs/Quapaw Community YWCA
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-92 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1982-90, n.d. (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1982-92 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1984-92, n.d. (Box 895)
    - California
      - General, 1993-94, 1998 (Box 895)
      - Alameda County, Southern (Hayward), [see also Oakland]
        - Accreditation requirements, 1988-93 (Box 895)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1977-81 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1988-95, n.d. (Box 895)
        - Merger with Oakland, proposal, 1991 (Box 895)
      - Bakersfield
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 895)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1985-96 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1984-95, n.d. (Box 895)
      - Berkeley Community, [see also RECORD GROUP 7. - SERIES XI. - Student Associations, Univ of California at Berkeley]
        - Correspondence and notes, 1988-95 (Box 895)
        - Organization/Structure, 1973-92, n.d. (Box 895)
      - Contra Costa County (Richmond)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 895)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1990-97 (Box 895)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-98 (Box 895)
        - Annual Statistical Report, 2000 (Box 895)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1940-98 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 895)
        - Finance administration, 1989-95 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1991-97, n.d. (Box 895)
      - Fontana
        - Constitution, 1955-83 (Box 895)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 895)
        - Program, 1969-93 (Box 895)
      - Fresno
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 896)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-97 (Box 896)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 896)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-97 (Box 896)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1991-96 (Box 896)
        - Correspondence, 1990-98 (Box 896)
        - Finance administration, 1988-92 (Box 896)
        - Organization/Structure, 1990, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Program, 1996, n.d. (Box 896)
      - Gardena Valley
        - Accreditation requirements, 1992-99 (Box 896)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-98 (Box 896)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 896)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1975, 1996, 1998 (Box 896)
        - Correspondence, 1974-2000, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Program, 1985-97, n.d. (Box 896)
      - Glendale
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 896)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 896)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 2000 (Box 896)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 896)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-98, 2000 (Box 896)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1937, 1982-2000 (Box 896)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Program
          - General, 1982-2000, n.d. (Box 896)
          - Domestic Violence training materials, ca. 2000 (Box 896)
      - Harbor Area (San Pedro)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 896)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 896)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 896)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 896)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98 (Box 896)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1921, 1995-96 (Box 896)
        - Correspondence, 1995-99, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Program
          - General, 1989, 1997, n.d. (Box 896)
          - Lesbian Outreach Project, 1995 (Box 896)
      - [Hollywood Studio Club - see Series III.]
      - Humboldt County (Eureka)
        - General, 1970-88 (Box 896)
      - Long Beach
        - Board of Directors, 1991 (Box 896)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1958 (Box 896)
        - Correspondence, 1989-93, n.d. (Box 896)
        - Program, 1980-91, n.d. (Box 896)
      - Los Angeles, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 896)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-2000 (Box 896)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 897)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 897)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995, n.d. (Box 897)
        - Correspondence, 1972, 1992-2002 (Box 897)
        - Program, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 897)
      - Mid-Peninsula (Palo Alto)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 897)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 897)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 897)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 897)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98 (Box 897)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 897)
        - Correspondence, 1980-2002 (Box 897)
        - Program, 1992-99, n.d. (Box 897)
      - Monterey County/Peninsula (Monterey)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 897)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 897)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 897)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 897)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-97 (Box 897)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1991, 1996, n.d. (Box 897)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98 (Box 897)
        - Program, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 897)
      - Napa Solano (Vallejo), 1986-88 (Box 897)
      - Oakland
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-96 (Box 897)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-96 (Box 897)
        - Affiliation requirements
          - General, 1995 (Box 897)
          - Resource manual for Affiliation, Jan 2001 (Box 897)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 897)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1890, 1959, 1991, 1996, n.d. (Box 897)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box 897)
        - Program, 1983-99, n.d. (Box 897)
      - Orange County, Central (Orange)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 898)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 898)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 898)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 898)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-91 (Box 898)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1967, 1996, n.d. (Box 898)
        - Correspondence, 1989-98 (Box 898)
        - Legal: Nowotarski and Nowak v. Central Orange County YWCA, 1992-94 (Box 898)
        - Program, 1990, 1995, n.d. (Box 898)
      - Orange County, North (Fullerton)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 898)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 898)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 898)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 898)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1973, 1995-96 (Box 898)
        - Correspondence, 1990-99 (Box 898)
      - Orange County, South (Santa Ana)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 898)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 898)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 898)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1946, 1978, 1998 (Box 898)
        - Correspondence, 1992-98 (Box 898)
        - Program, 1990-97, n.d. (Box 898)
      - Pasadena-Foothill Valley (Pasadena)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 898)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 898)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998, 2000 (Box 898)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 898)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1946-98 (Box 898)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 898)
        - Program, 1985-2000, n.d. (Box 898)
      - Redlands